MkvDrama.Org
Mkv戏剧网
Episode 5
第 5 集
There is no need to be nervous.
无需紧张。
I will not rebuke you.
我不会责备你。
I was just asking.
我只是问问。
In the end, Hua Shen didn't receive much money.
最终，华神并没有拿到多少钱。
Lord, Your Majesty has sent a message.
陛下，陛下已经传话了。
He said that Mr. Jong was here.
他说Jong先生在这里。
And I'm looking for a mistress.
而且我正在寻找情妇。
OK.
好的。
Let's go to mother's house.
我们去妈妈家吧。
mother.
母亲。
long time no see.
好久不见。
Thank you for Richie, Mom.
谢谢你，妈妈，里奇。
Does it taste good?
这个好吃吗？
what's the problem?
有什么问题？
Master and Mistress really love each other.
师父和师娘真的很相爱。
We're really jealous of that.
我们真的很嫉妒这一点。
Senior, it’s been a while since I saw you.
前辈，好久没见到你了。
And I'm wondering what you're doing.
我想知道你在做什么。
I was busy with work
我工作很忙
So I took a break today.
所以我今天休息了。
Did someone give you a hard time earlier?
之前有人为难你吗？
Kian
基安
Why are you keeping everything to yourself now?
为什么你现在要把一切都留给自己？
You used to consult me ​​on everything.
以前你什么事都会咨询我。
i solved
我解决了
Mu Yao's hatred towards me
慕瑶对我的仇恨
And she doesn't want to kill me anymore.
她不想再杀我了。
But Jonggong, who had nothing to do,
但无事可做的宗公，
Before with my family
之前和家人一起
They started turning their backs on us.
他们开始背弃我们。
Can't the original ending be changed?
原著结局就不能改吗？
Where did I go wrong this time?
这次我哪里做错了？
Kian.
基安.
Kian!
基安！
You were dazed again. Did you hear me?
你又茫然了。你听到我说话了吗？
sorry.
对不起。
The scent here is a bit dizzy
这里的香味有点晕
So I haven't heard from you now.
所以我现在还没有收到你的消息。
The carriage has no scent.
车厢里没有任何气味。
But it smells.
但有气味。
Kian
基安
I think you have a lot on your mind.
我想你心里有很多想法。
After we got married.
我们结婚后。
you don't have to tell me
你不必告诉我
What are you thinking?
你在想什么？
Just remember that as long as I'm here
只要记住只要我还在这里
I will protect you.
我会保护你。
There is no need to go to the hostess
不用去找女主人
Even if I'm angry
即使我很生气
And you don't want to spend time with me.
而你却不想和我共度时光。
I won't go to you...
我不会去找你...
Unless you want me to do that.
除非你想让我这么做。
Am I really that kind of person...
我真的是这样的人吗...
Want to protect?
想要保护？
to let go.
放手。
late. It's better to go to bed.
晚的。最好去睡觉了。
Miss, my father asked me
小姐，我父亲问我
About the situation here a few days ago.
说起前几天这里的情况。
Are you my maid?
你是我的女仆吗？
Or my father's maid?
还是我父亲的女仆？
I am your maid, lady.
我是你的女仆，女士。
really?
真的吗？
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
Your father cares about you.
你的父亲很关心你。
After all, you've been here for years
毕竟你已经在这里很多年了
And the marriageable age is approaching.
而适婚年龄也快到了。
But you are not close to His Highness.
但你与殿下并​​不亲近。
i am afraid
恐怕
The person will be unhappy about it.
这个人会因此不高兴。
I lived in the servant's garden as he wanted.
我按照仆人的意愿住在他的花园里。
Why is he still dissatisfied?
为什么他还是不满意？
I only know the life of a maid.
我只知道女仆的生活。
It's in the hands of the owner.
它在主人的手中。
if they are not happy
如果他们不高兴
They can beat us
他们可以击败我们
Or sell us as you please.
或者按您的要求卖给我们。
All right. You may go now.
好的。你现在可以走了。
I'm going to sleep.
我要去睡觉。
OK.
好的。
government.
政府。
Don't wake me up.
别叫醒我。
I'll try to sleep some more.
我会尝试再睡一会儿。
I won't go to the Bell Garden today.
我今天不去贝尔花园。
What are you doing today, mistress?
小姐今天做什么呢？
Qian Zhi tried to wake you three times.
钱治三度试图叫醒你。
It will soon be noon.
很快就到中午了。
You have to wake up.
你必须醒来。
no.
不。
You are on fire.
你着火了。
Qianzhi, call the doctor.
千智，去叫医生吧。
OK.
好的。
Doctor Xia, how are you?
夏医生，你怎么样？
Master probably caught a cold last night.
师父昨晚大概感冒了。
I'll prescribe some medicine
我会开一些药
And aromatherapy.
还有芳香疗法。
It's my fault. I slept like a log
我的错。我睡得像一根木头
And there was no sound of wind.
而且没有风声。
I looked at the window
我看着窗外
The hostess's room is open this morning.
女主人的房间今天早上开放。
How can you be so careless?
你怎么能这么不小心呢？
she's okay
她没事
She just needs to take the medicine.
她只需要吃药就可以了。
OK.
好的。
Be careful not to let her catch a cold.
小心别让她着凉了。
Please come this way.
请这边来。
thank you
谢谢
I was trying to make an excuse
我试图找借口
But now I have a good reason
但现在我有一个充分的理由
Don't go to Bell's Garden.
不要去贝尔花园。
If you don't want to go
如果你不想去
Just don't go, mistress.
只是别走，小姐。
You don't understand.
你不明白。
I go there too often.
我去那里太频繁了。
If you don't follow what happened yesterday
如果你不关注昨天发生的事情
It will look very suspicious.
看起来会非常可疑。
What happened yesterday?
昨天发生了什么？
Shende Hall
慎德堂
master.
掌握。
The hostess has a cold, but she will be fine.
女主人感冒了，不过她会没事的。
He prescribed medicine.
他开了药。
And she just needs to keep warm.
她只需要保暖。
all right. You better go now.
好的。你最好现在就走。
I will leave.
我将离开。
master.
掌握。
Teacher, are you going to see me?
老师，您要来看我吗？
It's better not to bother her now.
现在最好不要打扰她。
Send a message to Hua Residence.
给华府留言。
He must miss his family very much.
他一定非常想念他的家人。
When she is sick.
当她生病的时候。
OK.
好的。
Master, please eat this before you go to sleep.
主人，请在睡觉前吃这个。
Is it too bitter?
是不是太苦了？
I prepared preserved fruit for you.
我给你准备了果脯。
government.
政府。
not needed. This is nothing.
不需要。这不重要。
Teacher, Deacon J has arrived.
老师，J执事来了。
Hello, mistress.
你好，女主人。
what's the matter?
怎么了？
government.
政府。
There was a lack of manpower
缺乏人手
A new guard has just been recruited.
刚刚招募了一名新警卫。
Here is the list.
这是列表。
For inspection, hostess.
供检查，女主人。
not needed. You have experience.
不需要。你有经验。
Just do whatever you want.
做你想做的事吧。
Then I will leave.
那我就离开了。
majesty.
威严。
It's already noon.
已经是中午了。
Why isn't he here today?
他今天怎么没来？
I sent someone to inquire in advance.
我提前派人去打听了。
The hostess has a cold.
女主人感冒了。
cold?
寒冷的？
That person must be very sick
那个人一定病得很重
Because Master called the doctor.
因为师父叫来了医生。
bring me
带给我
The incense beads she sent me a few days ago.
她前几天送我的香珠。
You shouldn't leave it alone all the time.
你不应该一直不管它。
however
然而
Choose Nutrient-Dense Herbs
选择营养丰富的草药
In a warehouse for her.
在她的仓库里。
She is too thin.
她太瘦了。
Strangely enough, she is not in good health.
奇怪的是，她的身体状况并不好。
And they are prone to diseases.
而且他们很容易患病。
Yes, Your Majesty.
是的，陛下。
???Lord, hello. ???You can wake up.
???主啊，您好。???你可以醒来了。
Sit.
坐。
I heard you called a doctor earlier.
我听说你早些时候打电话给医生了。
What's wrong with you?
你这人怎么回事？
Are you feeling unwell?
你感觉不舒服吗？
naught.
什么也没有。
I just didn't sleep well last night.
我只是昨晚没睡好而已。
And when I woke up, my head hurt.
当我醒来时，我的头很痛。
So I asked to see a doctor.
所以我要求去看医生。
What did he say?
他说什么？
They said it wasn't anything serious.
他们说这没什么严重的。
And prescribed a sedative.
并开了镇静剂。
you are helping my mom
你在帮助我妈妈
to take care of household chores
照顾家务
And it's hard work.
而且这很辛苦。
I'm glad I can do it
我很高兴我能做到
Lord, share your concerns.
主啊，请分享你的忧虑。
I lost weight recently.
我最近减肥了。
There is so much to do here.
这里有很多事情要做。
If you are offended
如果你被冒犯了
Just invite your family.
只需邀请您的家人即可。
Isn't this your mother and sister?
这不是你的妈妈和妹妹吗？
Are you still in the city?
你还在城里吗？
my sister's birthday
我姐姐的生日
It will arrive in 4-5 days.
它将在 4-5 天后到达。
She is young and spoiled
她年轻又被宠坏
And he asked me to meet my father.
他让我见见我的父亲。
Mom had no choice
妈妈别无选择
But yesterday I tried to take her out of town.
但昨天我试图带她出城。
They set off to visit my father in the south.
他们出发去南方看望我的父亲。
And it will stay there for a while.
它会在那里停留一段时间。
Butler Meng lived there for many years.
孟管家在那里住了很多年。
And it rarely comes back.
而且它很少回来。
It is normal for a child to miss his father.
孩子想念父亲是很正常的事情。
we are very grateful
我们非常感激
Lord, thank you for trusting our family.
主啊，感谢您对我们家人的信任。
But I heard your Majesty say
但我听到陛下说
I asked to call the doctor this morning too.
我今天早上也要求给医生打电话。
What's wrong with my mom?
我妈妈怎么了？
Your Majesty is fine.
陛下没事。
She just gave orders to the doctor.
她只是向医生下了命令。
To prepare nutritious herbs
准备营养丰富的草药
And he sent it to his mistress.
然后他把它寄给了他的情妇。
I think someone has a cold.
我觉得有人感冒了。
cold...
寒冷的...
The female lead has changed a lot.
女主变化很大。
And it's more likable
而且更讨人喜欢
After she got married.
她结婚后。
No wonder Her Majesty treats her more kindly now.
难怪现在女王陛下待她更加仁慈了。
My mom is good at talking to him.
我妈妈很擅长和他说话。
So she naturally takes an interest in her.
所以自然而然的对她产生了兴趣。
It's true.
这是真的。
Be careful, mother.
小心点，妈妈。
go.
去。
This herb is valuable.
这种草药很有价值。
I will watch them move it.
我会看着他们移动它。
You do that.
你做吧。
I am going to see my sister now.
我现在要去见我姐姐。
Stop.
停止。
Don't run around.
别乱跑。
This is not our home, it is our species residence.
这不是我们的家，这是我们物种的住所。
Did you hear me?
你听到我说话了吗？
???Okay... ???Act confidently.
???好吧... ???自信地行动。
let's go...
我们走吧...
go.
去。
to let go.
放手。
do you know
你知道吗
Where does your mistress live?
你的情妇住在哪里？
We've never been here before
我们以前从未来过这里
And I don't know the way.
而且我也不认识路。
I wonder if it's convenient
请问方便吗
So that you can take me there.
这样你就可以带我去那里。
Can you do it?
你可以做到吗？
Sir, I have been here before.
先生，我以前来过这里。
I still remember the road.
我还记得那条路。
Are you the eldest son of the Hua family?
你是华家的长子吗？
Do you know me?
你知道我吗？
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
teacher
老师
Didn't you go see your sister?
你没去看你姐姐吗？
What is this place?
这是什么地方？
Shende Hall
慎德堂
It must be Master Zhong's study.
一定是钟大师的书房。
Did the maid notice?
女仆注意到了吗？
Does it look a little different?
看起来是不是有点不一样？
Sir, aren't all your concubines?
先生，不都是你的妃子吗？
Isn’t it different after all?
到底是不是不一样了呢？
Stop.
停止。
Tell me what you mean.
告诉我你的意思。
How dare you talk to me like that?
你怎么敢这样跟我说话？
Kian. mother.
基安. 母亲。
Didn't you leave before me?
你不是比我先走的吗？
Why are you so late?
你为什么这么晚？
Huang took me in the wrong direction.
黄把我引向了错误的方向。
So we decided to take the longer route.
所以我们决定走更长的路。
Qian, I heard you were sick.
钱，听说你病了。
You seem to have lost a lot of weight.
你似乎瘦了很多。
Mom, do you feel that way?
妈妈，你有这样的感觉吗？
Probably because we haven't seen each other in a while.
可能是因为我们已经有一段时间没有见面了。
Your father and I stayed at the clan house.
我和你父亲住在族宅里。
over a month
一个多月
Because what happened to your cousin
因为你表弟发生了什么事
In the Garden of Bells.
在钟声花园里。
we just got back
我们刚回来
I heard he got you into trouble again.
我听说他又给你惹麻烦了
Yes, I did.
是的，我做到了。
It's a very big problem.
这是一个很大的问题。
Kian.
基安.
You have never bought jewelry
你从来没有买过珠宝
since you got married
自从你结婚以来
So I bought some especially for you.
所以我特地买了一些给你。
For the past few days.
过去几天。
I have a lot of these.
我有很多这样的。
How can you say something like that?
你怎么能说出这样的话呢？
Your brother is really interested in you.
你哥哥真的对你很感兴趣。
And I bought all the good things
我买了所有好东西
In our jewelry store for you.
在我们的珠宝店为您服务。
He got me nothing.
他什么也没给我。
I know you won't be angry with me.
我知道你不会生我的气。
Stupid kid.
傻孩子。
You have the same blood.
你们有同样的血脉。
Of course she will forgive you.
她当然会原谅你。
You're right, mother. Qian is blessed.
你是对的，妈妈。钱有福了。
This house is really great
这房子真的很棒
And it's much better than my house.
而且比我家好多了。
That's not all. Even the servants here
那不是全部。就连这里的仆人
Look different from others.
看起来和别人不一样。
when i came
当我来的时候
I saw the maid
我看见女仆了
It's coming from my brother-in-law's study.
它来自我姐夫的书房。
she looks pretty
她看起来很漂亮
But I don't think I've ever seen her
但我想我从来没有见过她
Around you before.
以前在你身边。
Who is she?
她是谁？
Studying for a master's degree?
攻读硕士学位？
I have enough maids in my house.
我家里有足够的女佣。
I went to your lab last time.
我上次去了你的实验室。
I looked into it and found that there was a lack of manpower.
我查了一下，发现人手不够。
I will let Mu Yao go there and serve you.
我会让慕瑶去那里为你服务。
We were both friends in a past life
我们前世都是朋友
But she and Hua Shen didn't know each other at all
但她和华神根本不认识
So no wonder he didn't recognize her
难怪他不认识她
Why are you asking about his maid?
为什么要问他女仆的事？
I'm just asking
我只是问问
Huaxian!
华县！
Keep your head straight!
保持你的头正直！
You know Jong Ye-ran...
你知道钟艺兰...
his staff
他的员工
You're not the type of person who can design.
你不是那种会设计的人。
???I... ???You've always been a playboy
???我... ???你一直都是个花花公子
But don't get us into trouble!
但别给我们带来麻烦！
Kian, boil some. I was just asking.
基恩，煮一些。我只是问问。
I don't dare get involved with the staff here.
我不敢和这里的工作人员有任何瓜葛。
Now please shut up.
现在请闭嘴。
Don't talk like that.
别这样说话。
You know how my brother is.
你知道我弟弟的情况。
He just says whatever comes to mind.
他只是想到什么就说什么。
however
然而
Now Master, is there a maid next to you?
现在主人，您身边有女仆吗？
Doesn't he hate being served by maids?
他不是很讨厌被女仆伺候吗？
What do you know about that maid?
你对那个女仆了解多少？
Mother, what should we do now?
妈妈，我们现在该怎么办？
keep an eye on your son
留意你的儿子
Do not interfere in the affairs of the head family.
不干涉本家的事情。
I'm just looking out for your best interests.
我只是为了你的最大利益着想。
Why are you angry?
你为什么生气？
at last
终于
You have only one brother among them.
他们之中只有你一个兄弟。
And he will be your only family in the future.
而他以后将是你唯一的亲人。
Even if that person is a bit blunt
哪怕那个人有些直率
He still treats you sincerely.
他对你还是很真诚的。
Mother, you were always partial to that person.
妈妈，您总是偏心那个人。
Look what he did.
看看他做了什么。
Calling him dull is a compliment to him.
说他迟钝是对他的赞美。
listen.
听。
when i was pregnant with you
当我怀你的时候
He was only five years old.
他当时只有五岁。
He came to me every day
他每天都来找我
Ask when you will be born.
问你什么时候出生。
He said he would protect you
他说他会保护你
and i love you
我爱你
Please give a message to mom and dad
请给爸爸妈妈留言
After you go back.
你回去之后。
What is that?
那是什么？
“A small leak will sink a big ship.”
“小泄漏会沉没大船。”
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
Dad, do you know what my brother did?
爸爸，你知道我弟弟做了什么吗？
To the store he is in charge of.
去他负责的商店。
I don't think I need to say more.
我想我不需要多说。
Tell me what my brother did today
告诉我哥哥今天做了什么
Then he will understand what I said.
然后他就会明白我说的话。
The store is owned by the Zhong family.
这家店是钟氏家族开的。
My brother needs to be disciplined.
我的兄弟需要受到纪律处分。
Hwa Residence
华居
How about Qian?
钱呢？
That person looks weak
那个人看起来很弱
But I still feel energetic
但我依然感觉精力充沛
So I don't think she is seriously ill.
所以我不认为她病得很重。
exorbitant.
高昂。
???You’d better go now. ???Yes, ma’am.
???你最好现在就走。？？？是的女士。
Where is Shen?
沉在哪里？
he said
他说
That person didn't finish his homework
那个人没有完成他的作业
So he went back to his room.
于是他就回到了自己的房间。
Did he go back to studying?
他回去读书了吗？
Did the sun rise in the west today?
今天太阳从西边升起吗？
He must have sneaked out again.
他一定是又偷偷溜出去了。
To play with his friends.
和他的朋友们一起玩。
How can that be?
怎么可能？
Qian is still sick.
钱还在病中。
He's worried about her.
他很担心她。
So he won't go out and play
所以他不会出去玩
Times like this.
就这样的时代。
I know that?
我知道？
I am not worried about Qian’s marriage now.
我现在不担心钱的婚姻。
But I am worried about Shen’s marriage.
但我担心沉的婚姻。
That person is not young
那个人不年轻了
But it's not stable yet.
但还不稳定。
Don't rush.
别着急。
Qian is now Master Zhong's wife.
钱现在是钟老爷子的妻子。
There are many merchants in this town.
这个镇上有很多商人。
I want to become relatives through marriage.
我想通过婚姻成为亲戚。
He doesn't need to get married.
他不需要结婚。
But my son has no talent for reading and writing.
但我儿子没有阅读和写作的天赋。
It's not even an outstanding martial art.
连武功都算不上出色。
In my opinion
在我看来
That's not important
这不重要
Even if the girl is from an ordinary family.
即使这个女孩出身于普通家庭。
He can handle her easily.
他可以轻松对付她。
And you won't be bullied.
而且你不会被欺负。
Even if that person is no exception
就算那个人也不例外
He is still our only son.
他仍然是我们唯一的儿子。
Daughters from ordinary families
普通家庭的女儿
You can't marry into my family.
你不能嫁入我家。
I know what you mean.
我明白你的意思。
But think about it.
但想一想。
Shen has many concubines.
沈氏有很多妃子。
When a nobleman's daughter marries him
当一个贵族的女儿嫁给他时
And then I found out
然后我发现
She will be angry.
她会生气。
He must be disciplined.
他必须遵守纪律。
I never stopped him.
我从来没有阻止过他。
From taking a concubine
从纳妾开始
But he still goes out and plays around.
但他还是出去玩。
A man must be ambitious
男人一定要有野心
But he's acting stupid
但他表现得很愚蠢
With his concubines all day long.
整天和他的妃子在一起。
when i go there
当我去那里时
There isn't even enough space for me.
连我的空间都不够了。
OK...
好的...
Don't be angry.
别生气。
you are right I must discipline that person.
你是对的 我必须管教那个人。
Curb his rash behavior.
遏制他鲁莽的行为。
wait.
等待。
This is strange.
这很奇怪。
???what? ???Aren’t you always on his side?
？？？什么？???你不是一直站在他这边吗？
What happened today?
今天发生了什么？
Why the sudden change?
为何突然发生转变？
Did he cause trouble at the bell residence?
他是不是在钟宅闹事了？
no...
不...
me...
我...
I just noticed that
我刚刚注意到
Policing has matured
警务已经成熟
after getting married
结婚后
And Shen can't live up to her.
而沉也不能辜负她。
Store Director
店长
she has changed so much
她改变了很多
After getting married.
结婚后。
What did she say to you today?
她今天对你说了什么？
Nothing, just minor things.
没什么，只是一些小事。
Let me remove these.
让我删除这些。
self...
自己...
Honey, don’t worry about Shen’s marriage.
亲爱的，别担心沉的婚姻。
???You’re really handsome. ???right?
???你真的很帅。？？？正确的？
He has white skin and long eyelashes.
他皮肤白，睫毛长。
right?
正确的？
You fell in love with him.
你爱上了他。
What about the racket?
球拍呢？
The mistress is sick. Quiet.
女主人有病。安静的。
Qianzhi, I told you many times.
千之，我跟你说过很多次了。
Gently.
轻轻地。
Don't act like this all the time.
不要总是这样。
I think you're the loudest here.
我认为你是这里最吵闹的。
What happen?
发生什么事？
What are you so happy about?
你有什么好高兴的？
Didn’t you hear, Mistress?
小姐你没听见吗？
Several new guards were recruited.
招募了几名新警卫。
G. Butler mentioned it to me.
G.巴特勒向我提到过这一点。
what's the matter?
怎么了？
One of them is so handsome
其中一位好帅
The maids went to check on him.
侍女们前去查看他的情况。
really?
真的吗？
But it doesn't leave much of an impression.
但并没有给人留下太多印象。
Of this handsome security guard.
这位帅气的保安。
Mistress, you were sick the day he joined us.
夫人，他加入我们的那天您就病了。
So you've never seen him.
所以你从来没有见过他。
Lady, you too will be surprised.
女士，你也会感到惊讶。
When I finally met him.
当我终于见到他的时候。
I have never seen such a handsome man.
我从未见过如此英俊的男人。
You both are so ignorant.
你们两个都太无知了。
He's just a security guard.
他只是一名保安。
What good is His beauty?
他的美丽有什么用呢？
if you've ever seen him
如果你见过他
You wouldn't say that.
你不会这么说。
I am not as ignorant as you.
我不像你那么无知。
After hearing what you said
听了你的话后
I miss him.
我很想念他。
Mistress, you are still recovering.
小姐，你的身体还在恢复中。
By the way, he is just a servant.
顺便说一句，他只是一个仆人。
no one in the world
世界上没有人
It can be compared to Master Zhong.
可以类比钟大师。
It was just a passing comment.
这只是一个路过的评论。
Master's birthday is 15 days away.
距离师父生日还有15天。
What are your plans, mistress?
女主人你有什么计划吗？
birthday?
生日？
Master's birthday!
师父生日啦！
Have you forgotten, mistress?
老婆你忘了吗？
What is Jong Ye-ran’s birthday?
钟艺兰的生日是哪一天？
I forgot
我忘了
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Isn’t that the beginning of a relationship
这不是一段关系的开始
Between him and Mu Yao?
他和沐瑶之间？
Teacher, it's late.
老师，来晚了。
Now it's time to go back.
现在是时候回去了。
Today is your birthday.
今天是你的生日。
I want to stay with my mom longer.
我想和妈妈待得更久一些。
Why are you kneeling here?
你为什么跪在这里？
Did your parents punish you too?
你的父母也惩罚过你吗？
No one punished me.
没有人惩罚我。
I do it of my own volition.
我是自愿这么做的。
what's the matter?
怎么了？
Why do you want to kneel here?
为什么要跪在这里？
My mom's tablet is here.
我妈妈的平板电脑在这里。
My father often says
我父亲常说
Parents want to see their children
父母想要见到他们的孩子
Live a happy and carefree life.
过着幸福无忧无虑的生活。
What do you think?
你怎么认为？
your mom wants you
你妈妈想要你
kneel in front of the tablet
跪在平板电脑前
With a sad face?
满脸悲伤？
I've never met her before.
我以前从未见过她。
the day i was born
我出生的那天
she...
她...
Every mother loves her children.
每个母亲都爱她的孩子。
He's probably on his knees
他可能跪在地上
I already broke her heart.
我已经伤透了她的心。
Would you like to go to the theater with me?
你愿意和我一起去看戏吗？
I was told that this temple carries our prayers.
有人告诉我这座寺庙承载着我们的祈祷。
Let's go pray together.
我们一起去祈祷吧。
OK. Now that I have brought you here
好的。既然我把你带到了这里
I will go to my father.
我会去找我父亲。
What is your name?
你叫什么名字？
my father said
我父亲说
You shouldn't say my name to strangers.
你不应该对陌生人说出我的名字。
Can I see your face?
我可以看看你的脸吗？
no. There's a rash on her face
不。我脸上有皮疹
So I can't take off the veil.
所以我无法摘下面纱。
This is for you.
这是给您的。
If you want to see me again next time
如果你下次还想再见到我
just show me
给我看看
To the abbot of this temple.
至此寺方丈。
Okay... I'll take it.
好吧...我会接受的。
Seeing you around.
看见你在身边。
Mom, I will visit you another day.
妈妈，我改天再去看你。
Oh my god
天哪
If you want to give me another chance
如果你想再给我一次机会
Why didn't you send me back
你为什么不送我回去
Before I impersonated her?
在我冒充她之前？
It's too difficult to turn back now.
现在想回头太难了。
government.
政府。
OK.
好的。
How will you plan your birthday party?
你将如何计划你的生日聚会？
Wait a minute.
等一下。
I remember that day
我记得那天
The Lord came to the banquet unexpectedly
主不期而遇
And falls in love with Mu Yao at first sight
并对慕瑶一见钟情
That person treated me like that a few days ago.
几天前那个人就是这样对待我的。
Now is the perfect time to distract him
现在是分散他注意力的最佳时机
So he won't be preoccupied with it
所以他不会全神贯注于它
Acts that harm my family
伤害我家人的行为
Let's keep it quiet.
让我们保持安静。
After all, it belongs to his mother too...
毕竟，这也是他母亲的……
I don't think he would like the fanfare.
我认为他不会喜欢大张旗鼓。
Lady, how about I go to the warehouse now?
女士，我现在去仓库怎么样？
And will you take back the guchin that Master gave you?
那么你会收回师父给你的guchin吗？
Exquisite Guqin
精致的古琴
And your excellent playing skills
还有你出色的演奏技巧
It will definitely surprise everyone.
绝对会让大家大吃一惊。
not needed.
不需要。
yes. Go get it.
是的。去实现它（梦想）;去得到它（东西。
confident.
自信的。
master.
掌握。
The mistress's maid Qianzhi wants to meet you.
女主人的丫鬟千织要见你。
Hello, Master.
你好，师父。
The hostess asked me to send her a message.
女主人让我给她发消息。
she wants you to come back early
她希望你早点回来
After work today.
今天下班后。
She prepared a birthday feast for you.
她为你准备了一顿生日宴。
not needed. I never celebrate my birthday.
不需要。我从不庆祝我的生日。
But she started preparing for it
但她已经开始准备了
Half a month ago.
半个月前。
OK.
好的。
Shende Hall
慎德堂
Guchin is ready.
Guchin已准备就绪。
Should I take it out now?
我现在应该把它拿出来吗？
not needed. Follow my lead later.
不需要。稍后跟随我的引导。
But please put another chair here.
但请在这里再放一把椅子。
May the Lord sit down.
愿主坐下。
Is he coming too?
他也来吗？
Master didn't mention it.
师父没有提到。
Just trust me.
相信我。
The quality of this batch of blood pumpkins
这批血南瓜的品质
Not as good as the previous batch.
不如上一批。
If you use this to make gainhwan,
如果你用这个来制作增益焕，
It will be much less effective
效果会差很多
That will ruin our reputation.
那会毁掉我们的声誉。
In case of insufficient supply
如果供应不足
I'm worried we might have to sell it.
我担心我们可能不得不卖掉它。
The number of pills decreases every year.
药丸的数量逐年减少。
difference.
不同之处。
difference!
不同之处！
what's the matter?
怎么了？
Is there anything else to do?
还有什么事情要做吗？
Lord.
主。
I have other things to do today.
我今天还有其他事情要做。
Let's synthesize the perfume another day.
改天我们来合成香水吧。
I almost forgot.
我差点忘了。
Are you going to the temple again this year?
今年你还去寺庙吗？
No, it doesn't.
不，事实并非如此。
When I left this morning
当我今天早上离开时
Qian sent a message
钱发来消息
They said they prepared a banquet.
他们说他们准备了一场宴会。
And I decided to go back early today.
我决定今天早点回去。
I would like to attend this banquet.
我愿意参加这个宴会。
Because it piqued your interest.
因为它激起了你的兴趣。
It's just a family meal.
这只是一顿家庭聚餐。
i will be happy
我会很开心
If you go with me, Lord.
如果你跟我走，主啊。
I'll change into different clothes.
我会换上不同的衣服。
OK.
好的。
Hello, Lord.
你好，主啊。
Today is my senior’s birthday.
今天是我学长的生日。
I'm just following along.
我只是跟着。
There is no need for that format.
不需要那种格式。
Mistress, you were right.
小姐，你说得对。
Lord, you have really come.
主啊，你真的来了。
Go get ready.
去准备吧。
I think you have a cook in your house.
我想你家里有一个厨师。
I'm very good at making spicy food.
我很擅长做辛辣的食物。
The owner likes this taste
楼主喜欢这个味道
So I spoke specifically to the chef today.
所以我今天专门跟厨师聊了聊。
Master has been feeling unwell these days.
师父这几天身体不太舒服。
The doctor told him to avoid spices.
医生告诉他要避免使用香料。
Should I ask the chef to make other dishes as well?
我应该请厨师做其他菜吗？
are you okay. I am already much better now.
你还好吗。我现在已经好多了。
Mistress, I am ready for you.
小姐，我已经准备好迎接你了。
It's a bit boring to just eat it.
光吃就有点无聊了。
Previously, Master gave me a rare Guqin.
之前师父送了我一把难得的古琴。
today is your birthday
今天是你的生日
So I brought it out for you today.
所以今天我就给大家带来了。
I heard that Mo Yao is very good at acting Guqin.
听说莫瑶古琴演奏得很好。
I wonder
我想知道
If only I could play a song for the master.
如果我能为大师演奏一首歌就好了。
government...
政府...
Do you need anything else, Mu Yao?
慕瑶，你还需要什么吗？
In my past life, I played songs first
前世是我先放歌
And provoked Mu Yao
还激怒了沐瑶
But that caused me a lot of trouble.
但这给我带来了很多麻烦。
This time we'll help you make her famous
这次我们将帮助您让她出名
So she doesn't have to use me.
所以她不必使用我。
There is so much talent in your abode.
你的住所里人才辈出。
Even a simple maid can play such beautiful music.
即使是一个普通的女仆也能演奏出如此美妙的音乐。
Its amazing.
太奇妙了。
You are praising her.
你这是在夸她。
Her playing is very average.
她的演奏很普通。
you're welcome.
不客气。
the music this woman played
这个女人演奏的音乐
It conveys the heroic spirit of soldiers.
传达了军人的英雄气概。
Even famous musicians
就连著名的音乐家
Not as good as her.
还不如她。
It's just normal to me.
这对我来说很正常。
then...
然后...
Why don't you give her to me?
你为什么不把她交给我？
My mom likes music.
我妈妈喜欢音乐。
She can relieve boredom.
她可以缓解无聊。
Bonus video
奖励视频
Bodyguard selection is over
保镖选拔结束
G. Butler picked the agile ones.
G.巴特勒选择了敏捷的。
Are any of them talented?
他们中有人有才华吗？
when i was watching
当我在看的时候
I found a nimble man.
我找到了一个敏捷的人。
I don't think I learned any martial arts.
我想我没有学过任何武术。
But he could handle the pros very well.
但他可以很好地应对职业选手。
Does that make him a natural martial artist?
这是否使他成为一个天生的武术家？
Rather
相当
Rather, it felt like I was risking my life.
相反，感觉就像我在拿自己的生命冒险。
No matter how strong the opponent is
不管对手有多强
They will inevitably feel a little afraid
他们难免会感到有点害怕
When I fought him.
当我和他战斗的时候。
who. Put him down.
WHO。把他放下来。
OK.
好的。
Just go in and register.
进去注册就可以了。
From now on, you will be living in the security room.
从现在开始，你就住在保安室了。
Thank you, Deacon Ji.
谢谢你，季执事。
Coach him later.
以后再辅导他吧。
If you have a personality like this
如果你有这样的性格
really you can use
你真的可以使用
He will never betray you.
他永远不会背叛你。
famous.
著名的。
wait.
等待。
What is your name?
你叫什么名字？
Huarongzhou.
华容洲。